<xml version="1.1">
<class name="ReadStrategy">
<legal>
Copyright (c) 2015-2017 Mike Goppold von Lobsdorf

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along
with this program; if not, write to the Free Software Foundation, Inc.,
51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301 USA.
</legal>
<desc>
This class contains information about making a
good and strategic read from the stream.
</desc>
<body>

<var name="readAheadAmount"><desc>
An amount, in code units.
Tells how much to read ahead of the current index.
A minimum read ammount, unless at the end of
the stream.
</desc></var>

<var name="readBehindAmount"><desc>
An amount, in code units.
Tells how much to read behind of the current index.
A minimum read ammount, unless at the beginning of
the stream.
</desc></var>

<var name="minAheadAmount"><desc>
An amount, in code units.  Tells how much data
must be in the buffer after currentIndex.
</desc></var>

<var name="minBehindAmount"><desc>
An amount, in code units.  Tells how much data
must be in the buffer before currentIndex.
</desc></var>

<var name="readDirection"><desc>
See ReadDirection.
</desc></var>

<var name="specificBufferSize"><desc>
An amount, in code units,
that tells the capacity of a new
BufferElement.
</desc></var>

<var name="idealBufferSize"><desc>
An amount, of an ideal total excerpt
size.  Holding more is unnecessary.
</desc></var>

<var name="idealSpecificBufferCount"><desc>
An ideal number of BufferElements
to retain.  Holding more is unnecessary.
</desc></var>

</body>
</class>
</xml>
