<xml version="1.1">
<class name="TokenHelperData">
<legal>
Copyright (c) 2015-2017 Mike Goppold von Lobsdorf

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along
with this program; if not, write to the Free Software Foundation, Inc.,
51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301 USA.
</legal>
<desc>
Data about a potential token.  Token helpers
generally seek the longest possible token.
It helps in differentiating among multiple potential tokens.
</desc>
<body>

<constant name="STATE_CONTINUE"><desc>
Indicates a token helper isnt done processing.
</desc></constant>

<constant name="STATE_DONE"><desc>
State that indicates a token helper is done processing.
The end of the token is pastIndex.  This result
is reported by regular token helpers.
</desc></constant>

<constant name="STATE_PAST"><desc>
State that indicates the helper is done processing.
</desc></constant>

<var name="match"><desc>
True if there is a match.
(Only the longest one is remembered.)
</desc></var>

<var name="resultLength"><desc>
The length of the result token.
</desc></var>

<var name="startIndex"><desc>
The start index of the result token.
</desc></var>

<var name="pastIndex"><desc>
The past index of the result token.
</desc></var>

<var name="currentIndex"><desc>
<p>
The stream index that the helper is at.
This index can be one character behind,
in the reading process.
</p>
<p>
Many token helpers use this variable.
</p>
</desc></var>

<var name="radix"><desc>
<p>
The current radix, for handling digits.
The max is usually 16.
</p>
<p>
Many token helpers use this variable.
</p>
</desc></var>

<var name="unsureLength"><desc>
<p>
Length of a span,
that may/may-not be part of the token.
</p>
<p>
If processing this span is successful,
then it will be added to resultLength.
</p>
<p>
Many token helpers use this variable.
</p>
</desc></var>

<var name="unsure"><desc>
<p>
Tells if the helper is currently processing
an unsure span.
</p>
<p>
If true, the parser is unsure,
that the span, starting from resultLength,
with length unsureLength,
will be in the final token.
</p>
<p>
Many token helpers use this variable.
</p>
</desc></var>

</body>
</class>
</xml>
